let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Nigeria is divided into 36 states. Which one is the largest by area?",
    answer: "Niger State",
    options: ["Adamawa State", "Niger State", "Kano State", "Zamfara State"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which planet is closest to the sun?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: ["Pluto", "Venus", "Mercury", "Jupiter"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many ribs are in a human body?",
    answer: "24",
    options: ["18", "24", "20", "32"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: " How many dots appear on a pair of dice?",
    answer: "42",
    options: ["42", "34", "32", "26"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "NYSC was established in what year?",
    answer: "1973",
    options: ["1987", "1973", "1983", "1974"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A group of Cow is called",
    answer: "A Murder",
    options: ["A School", "A Diary", "A Murder", "A Column"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many local governments are in Lagos? ",
    answer: "20",
    options: ["24", "20", "34", "27"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "RCCG was founded in what year",
    answer: "1952",
    options: ["1952", "1956", "1965", "1971"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is your body's largest organ?",
    answer: "Skin",
    options: ["Skin", "Bone", "Blood", "Hair"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The world largest ocean is?",
    answer: "Pacific Ocean",
    options: ["Atlantic Ocean", "Pacific Ocean", "Indian Ocean", "Artic Ocean"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question:
      "If the time in Nigeria is 12 Noon, what is the time in a country with time zone GMT-2",
    answer: "9AM",
    options: ["10AM", "9AM", "2PM", "11AM"],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "15 x 15 + 20 = ?",
    answer: "245",
    options: ["50", "250", "245", "315"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "How many cupcakes are in a baker's dozen ?",
    answer: "13 cupcakes",
    options: ["13 cupcakes", "12 cupcakes", "24 cupcakes", "10 cupcakes"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is Cynophobia?",
    answer: "Fear of Dogs",
    options: [
      "Fear of oxygen",
      "Fear of Dogs",
      "Fear of spices",
      "Fear of Meat",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which country invented ice cream?",
    answer: "China",
    options: ["USA", "Holland", "China", "Argentina"],
  },
];
